<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[HEADNET]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[HEADNET]]></description>
        <link>http://headnet.dk/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 13:34:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://headnet.dk/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 13:32:12 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/db2c62ce-7cb7-4212-9efe-6e1a1ae97688.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://headnet.dk/we-wish-everyone-a-merry-christmas-and-a-happy-new-year/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e78cfc6d-362c-49e1-9a64-b52940dde216</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 13:30:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Headnet]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Headnet</h1><h2>We tech a more intelligent future</h2><p>We believe great people, great ideas and great software will continue to make our world more intelligent. We believe that we can co-create solutions that makes a huge difference for the way companies do business now and in the future.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://headnet.dk/about-headnet/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5d00134f-e8df-46bc-bf2d-5ab917a66283</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 13:05:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The future of web design]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The future of web design</h1><h2>Quick, easy websites</h2><p>Web designers have reason to be nervous because artificial intelligence (AI), web design, and programming have combined to form a new tool: The Grid. This is not another ordinary do-it-yourself website builder. The Grid is a revolutionary new platform powered by AI programming that takes your added content and automatically creates a unique look for your website. Your job is to provide content, choose what type of site you want, and hit publish. Once your job is complete, your new website is ready.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/822d461e-a6bb-40f9-81a4-8efd046d4808.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://headnet.dk/the-future-of-web-design/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9fa85359-4294-4868-b035-fd340c2c5d8c</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 13:32:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Piwik]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Piwik</h1><h2>A Google Analytics Alternative for the New Generation</h2><p>Gone are the days when having a basic website was enough to stake your claim in the internet world. Now, site owners are using web analytics to store data and compile reports about visitors’ behaviour and actions, and using this information to customize their sites and advertising. With over a billion websites in existence, actively managing and optimizing your site is essential to improving the user experience and increasing your web traffic and search engine rankings. In short, web analytics tools help you ensure your message is reaching as many people as possible in your target market.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5b479bf4-4c9b-4fff-9064-a0d70ce887a2.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://headnet.dk/piwik/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bd5b6c8e-cefe-4c0b-9934-a3a05195ac77</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 13:05:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Deep Learning Is Suddenly Changing Your Life]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Why Deep Learning Is Suddenly Changing Your Life</h1><p>Illustration by Justin Metz Over the past four years, readers have doubtlessly noticed quantum leaps in the quality of a wide range of everyday technologies. Most obviously, the speech-recognition functions on our smartphones work much better than they used to. When we use a voice command to call our spouses, we reach them now.</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/9198aa13b452f5bcb06de4055b3c1d01/noop.jpg?input=https%3A%2F%2Ffortunedotcom.files.wordpress.com%2F2016%2F09%2Flrn10_a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://fortune.com/ai-artificial-intelligence-deep-machine-learning/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3dd7c8d4-4ddf-4c83-8e43-d4ae06a18879</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 11:00:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Residence dating]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Residence dating</h1><h2>Making ideas become reality</h2><p>Before you can start a serious relationship or move in together, you have to know each other, maybe by meeting up for a date, having a laugh, comparing hobbies, and telling each other stories about your family and work. Also the other person’s style and appearance often have a big influence about whether to go forward or not. The purpose of a date is getting to know what type of person the other is and whether the connection is strong enough for you to want to continue seeing each other. When buying a house, the experience has many similarities, with many of the same feelings and decisions to make. As in the dating world, it is often difficult to get in contact with the person/residence. However, the technological evolution makes getting in contact easier and more convenient.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7b508261-0625-4ce3-b214-2cac65e2e5ce.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://headnet.dk/residence-dating/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">28787bdb-3b2e-4962-a261-64380a480879</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 11:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Finally, online after 60 years!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Finally, online after 60 years!</h1><p>Several phone calls to the office at Danske Filminstruktører have been similar to the following:</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/0f242dfd-9248-4a53-9bb2-48fc84026854.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://headnet.dk/finally-online-after-60-years/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d1bca939-51e2-4885-ba81-627129c679c9</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 11:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Copenhagen Marathon running app for DR]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Copenhagen Marathon running app for DR</h1><h2>Easy accessible digital presence</h2><p>In 2014, 25,000 to 30,000 people were expected to participate in the World Half-Marathon Championship in Copenhagen, and about 10,000 were expected to join the Copenhagen Marathon. But how is it possible to follow a race with that number of participants with different start times, extending over the entire city?</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/cfc60d07-1fb3-4099-9c5d-a71f23527de1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://headnet.dk/copenhagen-marathon-running-app-for-dr/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">003916bc-cf2d-4592-9c84-14c96324e72e</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 11:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>